## Siva Teja Mundlamuri

## **Software Quality Analyst**

+1 (203) 551-0324 | sivateja.mundlamuri98@gmail.com | 18 ½ Kinsley St, Nashua, NH, 03060.

Linkedin/siva-teja-mundlamuri | my-portfolio/siva-teja-mundlamuri

## **Career Objective**

Results Producing Quality Analyst with 2 years and 7 months experience in developing Java selenium-based automation test scripts. Highly skilled in Analysing, Designing, and Implementation of Quality Assurance testing Strategies for Web-based applications. Eager to contribute dedicated, smart work for product quality enhancement.

### **Skills**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, and Oracle SQL.

Tools: Selenium WebDriver, Selenium Grid, Jenkins, HP ALM, Jira, Confluence and Git

Frameworks: TestNG, Cucumber BDD, Serenity BDD, and Craft Keyword Driven Framework.

Methodologies: Agile, Waterfall, End-to-End (E2E) functional testing, and CI/CD.

## **Work Experience**

# Rivier University Adjunct Professor in Computer Science

Nashua, USA.

Jan 2024 - Present

- Taught Java programming (J2SE, JDBC, SQL & Algorithm Concepts) and web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), enhancing students' Programming and problem-solving skills.
- Helped students in designing web applications and preparing a research paper or journal.

# Cognizant Technology Solutions Software Quality Analyst

Chennai, India.

Jan 2020 - July 2022

Worked on insurance admin applications for Canada's Manulife and UK's Direct Line Group. In Manulife, worked on Ingenium which is used to handle health and life policies, while in DLG, worked on the Guidewire Policy Center and Claim Center which is used to handle home insurance policies.

- Responsible for analyzing system requirements or functional requirements and developing a test plan for the project based on SDLC.
- Writing, and executing Test cases and Test Scripts, tracking defects or bugs in Jira, after reviewing the business requirements and technical specifications.
- Developing and Maintenance of Automation Scripts using Java, Selenium, and CRAFT Framework.
- Regression testing using automation suites and debugging existing code and Fixing errors.
- Involved in Exploratory, Sanity, Smoke, System, Acceptance, and cross-browser Testing on web Applications.

### **Education**

# Rivier University, Nashua, USA. Masters in computer science

Aug 2022 - Dec 2023 GPA 4.0/4.0

Major Project:

URL of GitHub

- Developed a Java Selenium Framework integrated with Selenium Grid to distribute and execute test cases automatically across multiple systems in parallel.
- Achieved a 60% reduction in test case execution time.

#### **Achievements**

- STAR Performer Awarded at Project level for exemplary work.
- Hacker Rank Java Basic Certification
   Reference ID: 844E85C25867
- Hacker Rank SQL Intermediate Certification Reference ID: C935D8471F01